<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="edu.wpi.first.javadev.feature.core"
      label="FRC Java Development Core"
      version="1.0.8.5"
      provider-name="Worcester Polytechnic Institute"
      plugin="edu.wpi.first.javadev.sunspotfrcsdk">

   <description>
      Core toolset for FRC robot software using Java

Plugins that provide tools to program the FIRST Robotics Competition
cRIO in Java.  Includes ability to create new simple and iterative
robot projects, sample projects, and correctly modify the manifest
using Eclipse&apos;s integrated refactoring tools.  Also includes
launchintegration, with shortcuts to build, run, and debug FRC
Java projects. Includes a preference page to set team number
and file locations, as well as help content.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      * Copyright (c) 2009-2012 FIRST
* All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license>
      * Copyright (c) 2009 - 2012 FIRST
* All rights reserved.
*
* Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or
* without modification, are permitted provided that the following
* conditions are met:
* Redistributions of source code must retain the above
* copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following
* disclaimer. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the
* above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following
* disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided
* with the distribution. Neither the name of the FIRST nor the
* names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote
* products derived from this software without specific prior
* written permission.
*
* THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY FIRST AND CONTRIBUTORS``AS IS&apos;&apos;
* AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED
* TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY NONINFRINGEMENT
* AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO
* EVENT SHALL FIRST OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT,
* INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
* DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE
* GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS
* INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY,
* WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE
* OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE,
* EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.ui" version="3.6.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.core" version="3.6.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="edu.wpi.first.javadev.sunspotfrcsdk" version="1.0.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ltk.core.refactoring" version="3.5.100" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.core" version="3.6.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.ui" version="3.6.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ant.launching" version="1.0.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ant.ui" version="3.5.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.console" version="3.5.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.externaltools" version="1.0.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="edu.wpi.first.codedev.output" version="1.0.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="edu.wpi.first.javadev.launching"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.wpi.first.javadev.projects"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.wpi.first.javadev.sunspotfrcsdk"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.wpi.first.javadev.core.help"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.wpi.first.codedev.output"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.wpi.first.javadev.model"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

</feature>
